UMMI AMIRAH SOLEHAH SHUHAIMI

WEB DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Detail-orientated Web Developer adapt at making critical decisions, managing deadlines and conducting team reviews. With expertise in analysis and quantitative problem-solving skills, dedicated to company growth and improvements.



01112938548



ummieamirah98@gmail.com



926 A Jalan Sultan Mahmud 20400 Kuala Terengganu

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

Byond Tech Global Berhad | July 2022 - Present

- Resolved bugs in the HR Management System (Mysyarikat) Tools: PHP Yii, Yii2, mysql, javascript
- Developed, and managed Customer Relationship Management (CRM) Tools: PHP Laravel, Filament, Livewire, Alpine
- Developed intuitive and responsive front-end interfaces for the Job System
- Developed database schemas, tables, and relationships to efficiently store and retrieve data for CRM modules

Full Stack Web Developer

Aims Global Engineering Sdn Bhd | Aug 2020 - Jun 2022

- Developed and Managed HR Management Modules
- System Maintenance and Bug Fixing
- User Interaction and Data Collection
- System Presentation and Training

EDUCATION

Universiti Malaysia Terengganu

Bachelor's Degree in Science Computer (Software Engineering)

2018 - 2020

Engineering Matriculation College Kedah

Certificate of Higher Education in Civil Engineering

2017 - 2018

SKILLS

FRAMEWORK

• PHP Yii, Laravel, Bootstrap, VsCode, Livewire, Tailwind

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE

• PHP, Java

OTHER SKILL

• PhpMyadmin, xampp, sourcetree, github, git, mailtrap, sublime merge, Figma, mysql

REFERENCES

• Muhamad Syahmi Adib Bin Mohd suhaidi Programmer (Aims Global Sdn Bhd) syahmi.adib@live.com | 0129602150

• Nur Hasya Binti Nordin Web Developer (Byond Tech Global Bhd) nurhasyamohdnordin@gmail.com | 01114909117